mediabizbloggers.com 2017-03-28

# Privacy policy

MediaVillage.com ("MediaVillage") is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of our customers. The purpose of this MediaVillage privacy policy is to inform you, as a welcome visitor, what kinds of information we may gather about you when you visit MediaVillage, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. This privacy policy applies to the MediaVillage site. Please note that this policy applies only to MediaVillage, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. Our policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our customers' changing needs. All changes to our privacy policy will be posted here so that you are aware of our current practices.

### INFORMATION

MediaVillage collects personal information when you register with MediaVillage and use our products or services. When you register we ask for information such as your name, contact information, email address, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with MediaVillage and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. MediaVillage automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, MediaVillage cookie information, and the page(s) you request. All requested information on the MediaVillage site is not required. You may choose to post additional information about yourself. Please do not post sensitive data on registration pages such as credit card numbers, social security numbers or other personal data. MediaVillage is not responsible for your disclosure of personal information on our registration form, sound offs, blogs, postings or other product offerings. You have the option to change your posted data at any time.

### DISCLOSURE

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to MediaVillage or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies. MediaVillage may share such information in response to legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or in special cases such as a physical threat to you or others. And we may share with our Web site partners and prospective customers aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of MediaVillage.

### PROTECTION OF DATA

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

### HOW TO CONTACT US

We have established procedures to ensure that every reasonable effort is made to address your concerns. If you have any questions or comments concerning this policy, please contact [maryann@mediavillage.com](mailto:maryann@mediavillage.com)  or write to us: MediaVillage.com, Attn: Legal Department, PO Box 27740, Las Vegas, NV 89126.
